goroost.com 2017-04-09

# Privacy Policy - Roost

By using the Roost web site (“Service”), a service of Notice Software, Inc d.b.a Roost (“Notice”), you are agreeing to be bound by the following privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”). Notice reserves the right to update and change the Privacy Policy from time to time without notice. 

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail and sign up for services, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, aggregate information on service usage, and information volunteered by the customer. The information we collect is used to improve the content of our website, improve our products, and the quality of our service.

It is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes, except under the following circumstances:

It is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of [Terms of Service](https://goroost.com/pages/terms), or as otherwise required by law.

We will transfer information about you if Notice is acquired by or merged with another company.

#### INFORMATION GATHERING & USAGE

  * When you register for Notice Software products, including Roost we ask for information such as your name, email address, billing address, credit card information. (Customers who sign up are not required to enter a credit card for use of the free tier.)
  * When you register to receive pushes through one of our customers we receive a unique identification code that is assigned to your registration profile which also contains elements of your browsing history.
  * Notice uses collected information for the following general purposes: products and services provisioning, billing, notification targeting, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, and research.
  * Notice may use aggregated sets of collected information for the following general purposes: marketing, notification targeting, public relations, and research.

#### COOKIES

  * A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a website’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive.
  * Cookies are required to use the Notice websites.
  * We use cookies to record current session information.

#### DATA STORAGE

Notice uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to operate Roost. Although Notice owns the code, databases, and all rights to the Roost application. You retain the copyright to your content.

#### DISCLOSURE

Notice may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the [Terms of Service](https://goroost.com/pages/terms).

#### SAFE HARBOR

Notice Software complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Notice Software has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. If there is any conflict between the policies in this privacy policy and the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles, the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Notice Software’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>

#### SAFE HARBOR DISPUTE RESOLUTION

In compliance with the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles, Notice Software commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union or Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Notice Software at:

Notice Software  
300 Madison Ave, #270  
Toledo, OH 43604

OR 

support@goroost.com

Notice Software has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints for more information and to file a complaint.

#### CHANGES

Notice may periodically update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the email address you use to sign in to any of the Notice products.

#### QUESTIONS

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to [support@goroost.com](mailto:support@goroost.com) or by mail at:  
Roost  
234 5th Ave  
New York, NY 10001
